Viewers, wherever you are, we are saying to you -
the cage of sickness, poverty, isolation is as a result of unforgiveness.
Whether you are the accused or you are the accuser,
you find yourself in a cage of poverty,
you find yourself in a cage of affliction,
it must be - that is the root!
The root of poverty is unforgiveness.
The root of affliction is unforgiveness.
The root of isolation, depression is unforgiveness.
Unforgiveness is the root.
Tell your neighbour: The root of isolation is unforgiveness.
The root of affliction is unforgiveness.
The root of depression is unforgiveness.
The root of poverty is unforgiveness.
Whether you are the accused or accuser - that is the root.
Viewers, right now, it is time to begin to release yourself.
You have been in that cage of poverty, isolation, affliction, setback;
please, forgive whether you are the accused or accuser.
Jesus said, "Forgive them, they don't know what they are doing".
You are included!
Begin to forgive. I release your spirit, in the name of Jesus!
I release your spirit, in the name of Jesus!
Say, "Mercy!"
Mercy!
I can't hear you.
Viewers all over the world!
Mercy!
Again and again!
This is what you need now.
Open your lips now and say, "Have mercy on me, Son of David!"
Have mercy on me, Son of David!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, open your lips and begin to bind your body, soul, spirit
to the will and purpose of God for your life.
Viewers all over the world, be bound, in the name of Jesus -
to the will and purpose of God, in the name of Jesus!
Your soul, spirit and body - be bound, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, open your lips.
Mean it, with all your heart!
Wherever that disease is located, I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
It could be in your blood, kidneys, liver - out, in the name of Jesus!
Out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I command that weakness, if there is any weakness that is standing against you -
remember, it is not about your weakness, it is not about your setback;
I say, submit, in the name of Jesus!
Surrender, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Whatever you might have taken, eaten in your dream or from the table of your enemy -
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Whatever you might have taken in the dream from the table of your enemy -
I flush them out, in the name of Jesus!
By the power of the Holy Ghost! Holy Ghost!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Never a sickness Jesus cannot heal.
Never a disease or infirmity Jesus cannot cure.
Never a burden Jesus cannot bear.
Receive freedom!
Receive a relief!
Freedom!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, begin to talk in your freedom!
Freedom!
Breakthrough, in your health!
Freedom, in your business!
Breakthrough, in your finances!
Freedom, in your marriage!
Breakthrough, in your family!
Freedom!
Breakthrough, in your career!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I am waiting to hear the voice of breakthrough from you!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I believe!
I say, I believe!
The voice I'm hearing is the voice of freedom.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, begin to act freedom, act breakthrough, share your testimony with your neighbour.
Tell them your testimony!
That is it.
Viewers, begin to cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You are designed for freedom; you are designed for breakthrough.
Right now, cover yourself with the blood of Jesus!
Cover yourself with the blood of Jesus, in Jesus Christ's name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Amen!